<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Explore Prestige Portfolio Partners for all your insurance needs. From auto to home to life insurance, we've got you covered in the digital world.Protect your health and financial well-being with comprehensive health insurance coverage. Stay prepared for unexpected medical expenses.Get the best auto insurance coverage for your vehicle at competitive rates. Stay protected on the road with comprehensive insurance options.Protect your home and belongings with comprehensive home insurance coverage. Get peace of mind knowing you're covered in case of any unexpected events.Protect your loved ones and secure their future with life insurance. Get peace of mind knowing they will be taken care of financially.Travel insurance provides coverage for unexpected events while traveling, giving you peace of mind and protection during your trip.Find the best insurance providers for all your coverage needs. Compare quotes and choose the right policy for you. Protect what matters most.State Farm is a leading insurance provider offering a range of coverage options for auto, home, and life insurance needs. Get a quote today!Allstate offers a wide range of insurance products to protect you and your assets, with excellent customer service and competitive rates.Geico: Trusted insurance provider offering affordable rates for auto, home, and more. Get a quote today and save money on your coverage.Get comprehensive coverage with Progressive Insurance. Protect your assets and enjoy peace of mind with their customizable policies.Nationwide offers a variety of insurance products to protect your assets and provide peace of mind. Get a quote today!Navigating the insurance claims process can be overwhelming. Learn how to streamline and simplify your experience with our helpful guide.Filing a claim with insurance is crucial for getting the coverage you need in case of emergencies or accidents. Don't wait, file today!Discovering the truth behind insurance claims through thorough investigation. Trust our experts to uncover the facts.Insurance claim settlement ensures timely compensation for losses. Trust your insurer to handle claims efficiently and fairly.Navigating insurance disputes and appeals can be complicated. Get expert advice on resolving issues with your insurance provider.Subrogation in insurance: process where insurer claims against third party to recover payment made to policyholder for covered loss.Learn about insurance premiums and deductibles, key factors in determining the cost of coverage and out-of-pocket expenses for policyholders.Learn how insurance companies determine premiums based on risk factors and coverage options. Calculate your premium online for accurate pricing.Discover the key factors that influence insurance premiums and learn how to save money on your coverage.Understanding deductibles in insurance: Learn how paying a deductible can affect your coverage and out-of-pocket expenses.High vs Low Deductibles: Choosing the right balance can save you money on insurance premiums without sacrificing coverage. Find out more here!Discover the essential information you need to know about insurance policies in our must-read guide. Get informed and make smart decisions.Stay protected with insurance. Don't leave yourself vulnerable to unexpected events. Importance of Insurance cannot be overstated. Get covered today.Stay safe and secure with financial protection through insurance. Protect your assets and future with the right coverage for peace of mind.Insurance risk management: protecting against financial loss by analyzing, identifying, and minimizing potential risks for individuals and businesses.Understanding legal requirements for insurance is essential. Make sure you comply with regulations to protect yourself and your assets.Insurance brings peace of mind knowing you're protected financially in case of emergencies. Get coverage today for ultimate peace of mind.Secure your future with longterm planning. Get the right insurance coverage to protect yourself and your loved ones for years to come.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://finance.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo-512--512px13.png"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.1px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.a08a35ccacd7a428aa9a9edcb99290839:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.5px 49.5px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
footer{
background:#111111;
color:#ffffff;
}
.y4e1d202ef4158564310cfe3be6bfcc0c p,.y4e1d202ef4158564310cfe3be6bfcc0c span,.y4e1d202ef4158564310cfe3be6bfcc0c label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
.c01442b4db17de36472ab130e68549069 p,.c01442b4db17de36472ab130e68549069 a,.c01442b4db17de36472ab130e68549069 span,.c01442b4db17de36472ab130e68549069 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.c01442b4db17de36472ab130e68549069 a,.y4e1d202ef4158564310cfe3be6bfcc0c a{
color:#0b0b0b!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.y4e1d202ef4158564310cfe3be6bfcc0c a{
font-size:16px;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000!important;

}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.2px 30.2px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.5px;
padding-right:8.3px;
padding-top:5.4px;
padding-bottom:5.1px;
}
.w6f8ef911bd70a5c61489ff49a2572e8f{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://finance.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo-512--512px13.png" src="img/logo-512--512px13.png"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex navbar-nav ml-auto align-items-center"><li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" href="https://finance.netlify.app/news.html"  >News</a></li>
  
<li class="nav-item  dropdown">
<a class="nav-link tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de dropdown-toggle" href="https://finance.netlify.app/index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Prestige Portfolio Partners Types of Insurance Web Space</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/index.html"  >Prestige Portfolio Partners Types of Insurance Web Space</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/health-insurance.html"  >Health Insurance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/auto-insurance.html"  >Auto Insurance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/home-insurance.html"  >Home Insurance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/life-insurance.html"  >Life Insurance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/travel-insurance.html"  >Travel Insurance</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="nav-link tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de dropdown-toggle" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-providers.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Insurance Providers</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-providers.html"  >Insurance Providers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/state-farm.html"  >State Farm</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/allstate.html"  >Allstate</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/geico.html"  >Geico</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/progressive.html"  >Progressive</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/nationwide.html"  >Nationwide</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-claims-process.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Insurance Claims Process</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-claims-process.html"  >Insurance Claims Process</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/filing-a-claim.html"  >Filing a Claim</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/claims-investigation.html"  >Claims Investigation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/claim-settlement.html"  >Claim Settlement</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/disputes-and-appeals.html"  >Disputes and Appeals</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/subrogation.html"  >Subrogation</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-premiums-and-deductibles.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Insurance Premiums and Deductibles</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/insurance-premiums-and-deductibles.html"  >Insurance Premiums and Deductibles</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/calculating-premiums.html"  >Calculating Premiums</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/factors-affecting-premiums.html"  >Factors Affecting Premiums</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/paying-deductibles.html"  >Paying Deductibles</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/high-vs-low-deductibles.html"  >High vs Low Deductibles</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" href="https://finance.netlify.app/must-read.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Must Read</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/must-read.html"  >Must Read</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/importance-of-insurance.html"  >Importance of Insurance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/financial-protection.html"  >Financial Protection</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/risk-management.html"  >Risk Management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/legal-requirements.html"  >Legal Requirements</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/peace-of-mind.html"  >Peace of Mind</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://finance.netlify.app/longterm-planning.html"  >Longterm Planning</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" rel=nofollow href="https://finance.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Prestige Portfolio Partners</h1>
<p>At Prestige Portfolio Partners one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Prestige Portfolio Partners and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Prestige Portfolio Partners. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Prestige Portfolio Partners, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Prestige Portfolio Partners follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Prestige Portfolio Partners.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Prestige Portfolio Partners, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Prestige Portfolio Partners has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Prestige Portfolio Partners's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Prestige Portfolio Partners does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Prestige Portfolio Partners</br>
232-113-1826</br>
5733  King Street</br>
St. Louis, MO, 63101</br>
USA</br>
</br>
<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="42072e2b38232027362a082d2a2c312d2c042e3b7b022d37362e2d2d296c212d2f">[email&#160;protected]</a></br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 pt-5 container" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" href="https://finance.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" href="https://finance.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="tc7ba35ef31a7c94bf7eef012ed7d09de" href="https://finance.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
<p><p>The information provided on this blog is for general informational purposes only and is not intended as financial or investment advice. All content on this site is presented as general information and should not be taken as specific advice tailored to any individual&rsquo;s specific financial situation.</p>

<p>Before making any financial decisions, you are advised to consult with a qualified professional, such as a financial advisor or planner, to discuss your specific financial situation and objectives. The authors and contributors of this blog make no representations as to the accuracy, completeness, relevance, suitability, or validity of any information on this site and will not be liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use.</p></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script data-cfasync="false" src="/cdn-cgi/scripts/5c5dd728/cloudflare-static/email-decode.min.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
